<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE resources [
    <!ENTITY appname "SymPhoneic">
    <!ENTITY store_button "Store">
    <!ENTITY clear_button "Clear">
    <!ENTITY chord_prog_button "Show Info">
    <!ENTITY stop_recording_button "Stop Recording">
    ]>

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">&appname;</string>
    <string name="default_message">No pitch detected</string>
    <string name="store_button">&store_button;</string>
    <string name="clear_button">&clear_button;</string>
    <string name="chord_prog_button">&chord_prog_button;</string>
    <string name="help_desc">Help Button</string>
    <string name="star_desc">Favorite</string>
    <string name="help_title">Welcome to SymPhoneic!</string>
    <string name="help_text">This app is designed for use by musicians
        looking to find inspiration for chord changes in their songs.\n\nTo get started, first either
     record yourself playing notes that you want to use, or use the slider to manually select notes.
     Then, when you\'ve decided on a note, press the \"&store_button;\" button to save it. You can
        also press the \"&stop_recording_button;\" button to temporarily disable the microphone, then press
        the button again to re-enable the microphone. After storing one to three notes, press the
        \"&chord_prog_button;\" button to see common chord progressions involving the notes
        you\'ve selected.\n\nPress the ? button in the top right again to hide this menu.</string>
    <string name="scales_text">Scales</string>
    <string name="chord_progressions">Chord Progressions</string>
    <string name="notes_text">Your Chosen Notes</string>
    <string name="chord_progression_activity_name">Chord Progression Activity</string>
    <string name="favorite_activity_name">Favorite Activity</string>
    <string name="chord_help_title">Chord\nRecommendations</string>
    <string name="chord_help_text">This screen contains recommendation for scales and chord progressions
    that include the notes you selected. Press the star next to a chord progression to add it to
        your favorites. If you make a mistake, you can press the star again to remove it from your
        favorites. To view all chord progressions you\'ve favorited, press the star button in the
        top left corner.\n\nPress your device\'s back button to return to the previous screen, or press
        the ? button in the top right again to hide this menu.</string>
    <string name="scales_default">No scales found with the notes you selected. Please try a
        different combination of notes.</string>
    <string name="chord_prog_default">No chord progressions found with the notes you selected.
        Please try a different combination of notes.</string>
    <string name="chord_default">No chord found</string>
    <string name="favorite_title">Favorite Chord Progressions</string>
    <string name="favorite_help_text">This screen shows the chord progressions you\'ve added to
    your favorites. Press the star next to a chord progression to remove it from your favorites.
    If you make a mistake, you can press the star again to re-add it to your favorites.\n\n
        Press your device\'s back button to return to the previous screen, or press the ? button
        in the top right again to hide this menu.</string>
    <string name="favorite_default">No favorites found</string>
    <string name="favorite_desc">Favorite Button</string>
    <string name="start_recording">Start Recording</string>
    <string name="stop_recording">&stop_recording_button;</string>
    <string name="not_recording">Not Recording</string>
</resources>
